A Finding Aid to the Federal Art Project, Photographic Division Collection, circa 1920-1965, bulk 1935-1942, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Artist Files, circa 1920-1965; Series 1; Archival Resource Key; 9.6 Linear feet Boxes 1-24
  - New, Babette, circa 1936-circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Newell, James Michael, circa 1936-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 19)
    includes photos of Newell, circa 1937
  - Newell, James Michael, circa 1936-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Niberg, Abbey, circa 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Nickerson, J. Ruth, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Nicolosi, Joseph, circa 1936-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Nisanoff, Louis, 1937-1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Niswonger, Ilse, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Noble, Carl E., circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Nooney, Ann, circa 1937-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Nordfeldt, B.J.O., circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Norling, Ernest, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 29)
    includes photo of Norling, circa 1937
  - Norman, Geoffrey, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Novelli, James, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Nusbaum, Jesse, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Nye, Edgar, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Oldfield, Otis William, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Olds, Elizabeth (see also Dehn, Adolf), circa 1936-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 35)
    includes photos of Olds, 1937
  - Olenikov, S., circa 1936-circa 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Oley, Moses, circa 1937-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Opper, John, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Owen, Robert Emmett, 1939, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Owen, William, 1938-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Paine, Elizabeth, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Paleologue, Jean, 1938-1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Palmer, William C., circa 1936-circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 43)
    includes photos of Palmer, 1936-1937
  - Palter, Rebecca, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - Pandolfini, Joseph, 1937-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Paolo, C. S., circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Parish, Betty Waldo, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Parsons, Sheldon, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Pattison, Carrie A., 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Pecci, Mario, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Peck, Augustus, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Pels, Albert, circa 1938-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Penney, John James, circa 1937-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Pereira, I. Rice, 1938-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 10)
    includes photos of Pereira, 1938
  - Perelli, Victor, 1937-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Peri, Eve, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Perper, Marc, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Perry, circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Perry, Roland Hinton, 1936-1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Peterdi, Gabor, circa 1950; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Pettit, Grace, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Phillips, Bert, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Phillips, Elizabeth, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Phillips, Robert, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Picus, Robert, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Pierce, Leona, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Pine, Geri, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Pinto, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Pittman, Hobson, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Pleissner, Ogden M., circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Poirier, Emily, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Pollock, Charles, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Pollock, Jackson, circa 1937-circa 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Polowetski, Charles E., 1937-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Pont, Charles Ernest, circa 1936-circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Poole, Nelson, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Poor, Henry Varnum, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Poucher, Elizabeth Morris, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Powell, Arthur James Emery, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Powell, Leslie, circa 1937-circa 1945; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Preacher, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Prestopino, Gregorio, circa 1937-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Pusterla, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Pytlak, Leonard, circa 1937-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Quackenbush, Paschal, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Quilter, Ernest, circa 1938-circa 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Quirt, Walter, circa 1936-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Rabner, Tina, 1940-1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Raboy, Mac, circa 1938-circa 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Racioppi, Angelo, circa 1938-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 46)
    includes photos of Racioppi
  - Ramer, Nat, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - Ransom, Fosden, circa 1941-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 48)
    includes photos of Ransom, 1942
  - Raskin, Joseph, 1937-1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - Ratzker, Max, 1939-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 50)
  - Raucher, David, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - Recke, Gerard, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - Reeves, Ruth, circa 1939-circa 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 53)
    includes photos of Reeves, 1939-1940
  - Refregier, Anton, circa 1937-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 54)
    includes photos of Refregier, 1939
  - Refregier, Anton, circa 1937-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 55)
  - Reichman, Agatha, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Rein, Harry, circa 1936-circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Reina, Salvatore, circa 1937-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 3)
    includes photo of Reina, 1941
  - Reinhart, Stewart, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Reisman, Philip, circa 1937-circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 5)
    includes photos of Reisman
  - Reiss, Lionel S., circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Reiter, Freda L., circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Resnick, Milton, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Rexroth, Andre, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Reznikoff, Misha, circa 1937-circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Ribak, Louis, 1937-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Rice, Dustin, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Richter, Mischa, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Richter, Nathan, 1937-1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Ricciardi, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Rico, Dan, 1937-1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Rile, Hannah S., 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Rites, Marion, 1937-1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - River, Lowen E., 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Riza, Janet, circa 1938-circa 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Robbins, H. D., 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Roberts, Malcolm, circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 22)
    includes photo of Roberts
  - Robus, Hugo, circa 1936-circa 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Rodvogin, Harris, circa 1938-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Rogers, J., 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Rogers, Reginald Hubert, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Rohland, Paul, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Rohowsky, Meyers, 1939-1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Rohr, Julius, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Rollo, Joe, 1937-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Rolshoven, Julius, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 31)
    includes photo of Rolshoven
  - Romaine, Dorothy, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Romano, Emanuel, 1936-1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 33)
    includes photo of Romano, 1936
  - Ronay, Stephen, 1937-1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Ropman, B, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Rosalie, J., circa 1936; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Rose, Iver, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Rosen, Paula, 1937-1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Rosene, Helene, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Ross, Fred, 1937-1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Ross, Louis, circa 1938-circa 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 41)
    includes photos of Ross
  - Rothkowitz, Marcus, circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Rubitschung, Francois H., circa 1939-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Ruggles, Philo B., circa 1936-circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Rugolo, Joseph, 1940-1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - Rush, Olive, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Russin, Herbert, circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Russin, Robert, circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Rutledge, J., 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Saar, Richard W., 1945; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Sachs, Hugo, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Safferson, Matthew, 1940-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Saint Claire, E., 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Saint Cyr, 1936; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Saint-Lanne, Louis, circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Saltzman, Helen, circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Sambugnac, Alexander, circa 1937-circa 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Samuels, I. K., 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Sanchez, Juan, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 14)
    includes photo of Sanchez
  - Sanders, Adam A., 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Sanger, I. J., 1937-1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Sanger, William, circa 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Santoriello, Angelo, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Saphier, C., 1939-1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Sarka, Charles, 1938-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Sarkadi, Leo, 1937-1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Sasanoff, M., 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Savage, Augusta, circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 23)
    photo of Savage
  - Saviano, Thomas, 1939-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Sawyer, Archibald D., circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 25)
    photo of Sawyer
  - Scaravaglione, Concetta, circa 1936-circa 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Schafer, Marjorie, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Schanker, Louis, circa 1936-circa 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 28)
    includes photos of Schanker
  - Schardt, Bernard, 1938-1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Scheinberg, Clara, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Schewe, Theodore, 1937-1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Schiff, Luba, circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Schlazer, Michael, 1937-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Schleeter, Howard, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Schlemowitz, Abram, 1937-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Schmitz, Carl, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Schnitman, Sacha S., circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Schoonmaker, Eugene Spalding, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Schreiber, Georges, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Schulemowitz, Leo, 1940-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Schwardt, Marion, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Schwartz, Lester O., 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Schwartz, William, circa 1938-circa 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Scott, Marion, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Seabrooke, Georgette, circa 1937-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 45)
    includes photo of Seabrooke, 1939
  - Segura, George, circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - Sehlmeyer, Catharine, 1937-1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - Selinkoff, Alice, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 48)
    photo of Selinkoff
  - Sembler, Arthur, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - Sever, Alfred, circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - Shackelford, Shelby, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Sharp, John, circa 1937-circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Shaw, Lillian, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 3)
    photo of Shaw
  - Sheppard, William L., circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Sherman, Effim H., circa 1936-circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Shields, Francis Bernard, circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Shokler, Harry, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Shomberg, Bertram, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Shonnard, Eugenie, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 9)
    includes photos of Shonnard
  - Shore, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Shore, Arlene, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Shore, Lillian, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Shulgold, William, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Shulkin, Anatol, 1936-1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Shulman, Morris, 1938-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Shuster, Will, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 16)
    includes photo of Shuster
  - Sievan, Maurice, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Silver, Helen, 1940-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Simmonds, William G., circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Skolfield, Raymond, circa 1938-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Skoorka, Paul, 1940-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Slifkin, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Smith, David, circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Smith, E. F., 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Smith, Jacob Getlar, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Sofo, Arthur, 1938-1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Sokole, Miron, circa 1937-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Soles, William, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Solman, Joseph, 1937-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Soyer, Isaac, 1936-1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Soyer, Moses, circa 1938-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 31)
    includes photo of Soyer, circa 1938
  - Soyer, Raphael, circa 1936-circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Spagna, Vincent, 1940-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Speakman, Russel, circa 1936-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 34)
    includes photo of Speakman, circa 1936
  - Spector, George, 1937-1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Spivak, Max, circa 1938-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Spohn, Clay Edgar, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Sprinchorn, Carl, 1936; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Springweiler, Erwin, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Stamper, Mabelle Richardson, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Starr, Maxwell B., circa 1937-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Starr, Maxwell B., circa 1937-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Stea, Cesare, circa 1936-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 1)
    includes photo of Stea, 1939
  - Stearn, Frank, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Stefano, Berthe, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Steffen, Bernard Joseph, 1938-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Stein, Hirsh, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Steinback, William, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Steinberg, Abraham, 1937-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Steinberg, E., 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Steinlauf, Saul, 1940-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Stelback, Anna, 1937-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Stella, Joseph, circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Stenbery, Algot, 1938-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Steinfeld, Lawrence, 1937-1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Stern, Louis, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Sternberg, Harry, circa 1936; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Stewart, Dorothy N., circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 16)
    photo of Stewart
  - Stone, Louis K., 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Stone, Stanford Byron, 1939-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Stott, Joseph, circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Strack, Marjorie G., circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Straeter, Angela, 1938-1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Stuart, Edie, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Suba, Niklos, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Sulmonetti, Salverio, 1938-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Sussman, Richard, circa 1936-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Suzuki, Sakari, circa 1936-circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 26)
    includes photo of Suzuki, 1936
  - Swanson, Bennet A., 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Swerdloff, Sam, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Swinden, Albert, circa 1936-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Swisher, Allan, 1937-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Szanton, Beatrice, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Tait, Agnes, circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Takis, Nicholas, circa 1940-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Tamayo, Rufino, circa 1936; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Tamotzu, Chuzo, circa 1940-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Tanzer, Julius, 1937-1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Taskey, Harry L., circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Taylor, Douglas, circa 1937-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Taylor, Jack, 1936; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Terrel, Elizabeth, circa 1937-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Thal, V., 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Theobald, Samuel, 1939-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Thieme, Anthony, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - Thomas, Norman Millet, 1945; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - Thorp, George, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - Thrash, Dox, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - Tobias, Abraham, circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Todaro, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Todd, Bianca, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Tofel, Jennings, circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Tolegian, Manuel, circa 1937-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Trentham, Eugene, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Trevasani, N., 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Tromka, Abram, circa 1937-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Trubach, Ernest S., 1937-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Tschacbasov, Nahum, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Turner, Raymond, circa 1938-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 11)
    includes photo of Turner, 1940
  - Turner, Rene, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Turnbull, James B., 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Tworkov, Jack, 1937-1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Ubogy, Wolf, 1938-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Ufer, Mary, circa 1937-circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Ufer, Walter, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Ulreich, Edward, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Upjohn, Regan, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Usui, Bumpei, circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Vagis, Polygnotos George, circa 1939-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Valenta, Yaroslav Henry, circa 1937-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Van Aaltan, Jacques, circa 1937-circa 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 23)
    includes photos of Van Aaltan, 1938-1939
  - Van Raalte, David, circa 1936-circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Van Soelen, Theodore, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Van Wolf, Henry, circa 1939-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Varian, Dorothy, 1937-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 27)